DO YOU HAVE ANYONE ELSE TO TALK TO?
I JUST WANT TO STOP BEING INVISIBLE.
Baby.
Get up. You're gonna be late.
If you give up, they win.
What's this about?
All this "us versus them" stuff.
They're pressuring us
into selling them our business.
But we're going to stand firm.
And so will you.
Without Dídac.
Come on. Get up. I'll drive you to school.
Just like when you were little.
SARA'S BIRTHDAY PARTY!
THEME?
GLITTER, YOUR BODY, AND REVEALING ATTIRE
You're getting paid to take pictures
and videos at your birthday party?
That's wild.
The party's just an excuse
to celebrate that Iván moved in with us.
Maybe it'll cheer you up.
Totally! A little bling never hurts.
Even if it's only to mask your pain.
Fake it till you make it, babes.
I bet Iván will be there.
You should go and get to know him.
Jesus, Mom. You're so annoying.
I want no part in this.
Even if you popped both of us out,
he's not my brother.
Don't you want us to be a family?
Is that why you're doing this?
Or do you want his money?
Sweetie, you really have no filter.
Don't drag me into this!
Look, there he is.
Go tell him.
Say, "Hi. I'm your mother."
And leave me out of it.
You're so insensitive.
It's best if he gets to know me.
To know us. Before we tell him.
How would you feel if someone showed up
claiming to be your mom?
If a normal mom showed up,
I'd be thrilled.
Chloe, please.
We're a team.
We always have been. I need you.
Just leave me alone.
MOM:
HAVE YOU BEEN INVITED TO THE PARTY YET?
What's this?
It's for Sonia.
It's a vintage music player.
I made her a playlist.
- How did you share it using that thing?
- Dude. You record it with two-
I'll explain later. It's pretty involved.
What are you doing?
CHLOE'S PLAYLIST
What? Are you a little kid
desperate for attention?
PLAYLIST ADDED
Can I have that back?
Thank you.
I shared a playlist with you.
So you want to seduce me
with squatter songs?
I want to get to know you.
Through music, since you're not a talker.
You made that clear when we hooked up.
Did we hook up?
You love messing with me, huh?
Look, grand gestures
only work in the movies.
It's only a simple gesture.
Besides, we had some real chemistry.
Hear that? It's silence.
Silence, that's my jam.
And you just blew your chances
with that cringeworthy stunt.
Hey… I wanted to apologize.
Why?
I wanted to use you for sex,
and that was way out of line.
It's no big deal.
I was down for it at first.
Then I wasn't.
But it had nothing to do with you.
Yeah, but I just went right for it.
Yeah, you did.
I know it doesn't seem like it,
but I'm actually pretty socially awkward.
I don't really take the time
to meet people.
I suck at making friends,
and I made a bad first impression here.
So my weekend's looking pretty dull.
Come to Sara's birthday.
- Seriously?
- Yeah.
I'd love to, but I'm not invited.
It's my house too. I'm inviting you.
Okay.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- See you there.
- Yeah. Cool.
MOM: YEAH, I'VE BEEN INVITED
And what really pisses me off is
that this is driving me and Isa apart.
How is Isa involved?
Luis, maybe I should use the app
to talk about my private life, right?
It's an option.
But maybe you'd rather open up
to a human being.
Thank you so much. Really.
I was just upset the other day.
I'd rather not talk about me or my family.
Remember that my door is always open.
Shit.
- Looking for this?
- Yeah.
You left it behind.
- Thanks, Luis.
- Don't mention it.
PAU: COME ON. TALK TO ME.
YOU NEED TO LEARN THE TRUTH
ONCE AND FOR ALL.
It's a music player.
We can press rewind.
Go back in time.
Real subtle.
I told you that doesn't work in real life.
But the other night
was a second chance, right?
No, Nico. It was a mistake.
Back to your seats, please.
Let's open the app.
- Did someone make you a mixtape?
- A what?
May I?
Maybe you're not as alone as you think.
Who says I'm alone?
Sorry. That sounded creepy.
I've been watching you.
Well, you and everyone else.
Shit. That sounded better in my head.
- What I-
- No worries.
I know you're the app guy. Omar, right?
- Pleased to meet you.
- Same here.
I'm Sonia.
It's nice that someone cares around here.
You wouldn't need a volunteer, would you?
I'm a great helper.
You could really use someone
who is close to the students.
I really appreciate it,
but I've already broken too many rules.
I need to keep my distance.
Staring at us like that is kind of creepy.
No, it's not like that.
Joel is my boyfriend.
Helpers need help too.
I was contacted by tons of brands.
They loved the party idea.
They want more. It was a total success.
Between the party and Iván's rent payment,
we've made good money.
You were right, baby.
Not at school, honey.
The only thing they haven't seen
on IG is our butts. Come on. Kiss me.
Hi. Excuse me.
This room is for students and staff only.
- I'm Sara's boyfriend.
- So, student or staff member?
You're not helping.
You're only making him angrier.
Gather round, please.
Everyone in the showers too.
I'm going to offer
extracurricular self-defense classes.
Let me know if you want to sign up.
You can tell me in person
or send me a message.
I encourage you to join
because… the forest is full of wolves.
And you need to be ready.
Jessica, this is harassment.
No. I'm just monitoring a student
who needs help.
Not interested in the classes?
I don't like violence.
It's defense.
Sometimes, violence chooses you.
And you need to defend yourself.
You don't get it.
I do. Loud and clear.
Leaving Raúl is not an option.
Exactly.
So here are your options.
Stay with him
and pray to God that it all goes well
or learn self-defense
in case it goes wrong.
I went through the same hell,
and I chose the latter.
INTERMEDIARY: AS SOON AS I GET
THE PAYMENT, I'LL ORDER THE EVICTION.
Mom.
Honey, I came to meet with Virginia.
- See you at home later?
- I'll be with Nico and Eric.
- Are you going to that community center?
- I don't know. Why?
- They're gonna be evicted. It's not safe.
- Mom!
I stalled it as much as I could,
but my hands are tied.
Don't even think
about going there. Please.
THE SPIDER COMMUNITY CENTER
ART AND HOUSING FOR ALL
SELF-MANAGED COMMUNITY CENTER
We should be at the party already.
Leave your phones here.
We're having a meeting
to organize surveillance.
Surveillance?
- The cops are at the door.
- What?
LEAVE PHONES HERE
NEW MESSAGE FROM SONIA
NICO: COME TO SARA'S PARTY,
AND WE CAN TALK ABOUT STARTING OVER.
Falling for a present
and a song is kinda dumb, isn't it?
For a smart girl like you.
Ignoring my feelings
won't make them disappear.
I see.
I love this song. You should add it
to your playlist with Eric.
I deleted it. I'm onto something else.
Hey!
What's up? What's wrong?
Nothing. I'm just struggling
to keep it together.
Drink this, then.
Come on.
I'm not sure getting drunk is a good idea
with all this stuff on my mind.
It's only natural
you feel out of place after moving out.
I've moved a lot because of my mom.
I know what it feels like.
But at least you have your mom, right?
It's not the same with family.
Hey, my bad.
I didn't mean to be a buzzkill.
No, you're fine.
I used to move a lot with my dad too.
But now it's all just… more fucked up.
Yeah. I can imagine.
I mean, I can't, but I can try.
It must be fucked up.
I'm not good company tonight.
I'm gonna head to my room for a bit.
- See if I can get out of this funk.
- Okay.
Later.
MOM: IVÁN'S SUFFERED TOO MUCH.
HE'S STILL GOING THROUGH IT.
LET'S LEAVE HIM ALONE.
Why would my mom kill Amazona?
I don't know. To drive us apart, I guess?
It seems like it's working.
Why should we believe
your psychopath brother?
Just because he's your brother?
My mom is my mom.
Well, my brother also says
your mom ordered the shooting.
- Yeah, no.
- What?
- No, this is too much.
- I know it sounds crazy.
- This is just…
- I know it sounds crazy, Isa.
- It doesn't sound crazy. It is crazy.
- Yes, and I don't know who's done what!
I don't know who to believe,
but you saw how my brother
and your mom ended up.
Don't push me away, please.
We're fighting to stay together
no matter what.
Don't let them win.
Maybe they're right.
It's better if we're not together.
Then I guess they've already won.
- Damn.
- What is it?
I think these two just broke up.
Unless they communicate,
they're of no use to us.
Perfect timing, then.
The court denied our request
for the wiretap.
What are you going as? Unicorn diarrhea?
- I'll take over at midnight, okay?
- Okay.
- Aren't you off tonight?
- He's covering me for a few hours.
That's all.
See? You're already juggling stuff
to go to their parties.
What's next? Skipping class?
Losing your scholarship?
Omar, stop being so antagonistic.
- I'm not.
- You're always nagging me.
"Don't do this.
Don't do that. Las Encinas this…"
Can you please stop?
Either you trust me or you don't.
Come to the party.
Come. You'll see everything's okay,
and you won't get upset.
I've been to many of those parties.
And I have no business there.
Go and have fun.
Hello. Good evening.
You gotta be kidding me.
Hello.
God, I love this.
Hi.
Why the hell are you here?
What is life
if you don't crash a good party?
No, Mom. You're leaving.
It's obvious you won't help me
with your brother.
Stop saying he's my brother. He's not.
Okay. Whatever you say.
Either help or get out of my way.
I can handle this by myself.
Stay out of this.
I refuse to lose you forever.
Even if it's for the best.
Let me live with the hope
that one day we'll meet again.
Hello? Why are you here all alone?
Why are you here, ma'am?
Iván, don't call me ma'am.
We already know each other. Don't we?
Do you want some?
Are you okay?
That voice message sounded pretty intense.
Yeah, it is.
Or was. I don't know.
A long-lost love?
Is that why you're missing your own party?
It's not my party.
Every party can be yours
if put your mind to it, dear.
Tell me about the message.
Who was it? Or who is it?
My ex.
They say he ran me over.
Who says that?
The police.
And the evidence.
But I don't believe it.
That's why I keep thinking about it.
To figure out what happened.
What if you find out something unexpected?
Well… I don't know.
You need to be prepared
to handle the truth.
Otherwise, it's best not to know.
If the answer isn't what I'm hoping for…
I'm not sure how I'd cope.
Exactly.
I'm going to offer
some unsolicited advice.
Keep moving forward,
believing he's innocent.
Stop digging. Let it go.
If you keep dwelling on questions
from the past,
you'll miss out
on all the beautiful things ahead of you.
What beautiful things?
You'll see it. Trust me.
Once you let go of the shadows
of the past, you'll see it.
Trust me. There's a whole party
waiting for you out there.
Literally.
I have to disappear.
That's what everyone says.
So until we see each other again…
I love you.
- I love you so much, Iván.
- I love you so much, Patrick.
DELETE MESSAGE
CANCEL - DELETE
DELETE
It's my party, and my mom isn't here.
I don't know why yours came.
She's my guest. Don't worry, okay?
They both are.
They're helping me so much.
That's great, dude. That's what matters.
And excuse her.
Organizing this got us a bit stressed out.
It's okay.
All right? Cheers.
- Happy birthday!
- Want a drink?
Hi! Cheers!
- Want to dance?
- Later.
Okay. I'll see you out there.
God, he looks so happy.
It's good for him to have us around.
Great. Now you can leave.
Relax and smile.
I want to see you dance
and I want to see you smile.
Know what? I bet you would have abandoned
me too, given the opportunity.
Hey. What's this about?
Honey, it broke my heart to give Iván up.
Your arrival gave me a second chance.
So I was a band-aid?
You felt guilty,
and you had me to make up for it.
If you'd kept him,
I'm sure I wouldn't even exist.
Look at me, honey.
You're the most important thing I have.
You hear? The most important.
- I just want to give you a better life.
- Okay.
So could we both go back home now, please?
I'm making a lot of progress.
You go ahead if you want to.
I mentioned beautiful things.
There's one of them.
Hi.
I know I shouldn't say this,
but you look stunning.
Dídac, don't make this harder
than it already is, please.
I asked for space. Respect that.
Are you two having problems?
We're not having problems, darling.
Basically, we're not together.
I mean…
Honey.
Everyone!
Hey. How are you? Let me interrupt.
To all the gawkers and gossipers,
I can confirm it myself, okay?
Dídac and I are not together anymore.
Now, for the important thing. Honey…
Cheers to Sara, my friends!
Damn, Isa. That was a bit too much.
Well, it needed to be realistic.
If nobody knows we're together,
they won't try to split us up.
Wait. Can I tell you something?
When we argued today,
I felt like I was losing you.
Are you still listening in?
Luis, the order has been denied!
Yes, Luena. I know.
It's illegal!
I was thinking, we tend to take
the people closest to us for granted.
And today, I got scared.
I'm not going to push you away.
But we're going to have to play along
until we figure out
what's going on with our families.
Sure. That makes sense.
- It does.
- Yeah.
It makes a lot of sense.
I'd do anything for you, baby.
Baby? I'm dead.
What's happening?
All right. That's enough for today.
They can't come in for now,
but they're here to make us leave.
Motherfuckers!
END SPECULATION
What the hell?
- It's okay if we don't hit anyone.
- No one mentioned violence.
We're defending the hood.
We can't get out if they don't leave.
I'm out of here.
Nico!
Hey. Be careful, okay? Sneak out the back.
NEW MESSAGE FROM SONIA
NO BATTERY
Fuck me.
POLICE
Fucking pigs!
You bastards!
No police!
Come down. Hurry!
Let's go!
Grab something.
We should change clothes if we're leaving.
What if we hurt someone?
I still think defending ourselves
using violence is a contradiction.
Contradictions aren't always bad.
If you get involved, they're everywhere.
I was thinking…
of another contradiction.
How can you be so critical of Las Encinas
and be into someone like Chloe?
Chloe isn't what I thought she was.
Neither is Las Encinas.
- Not entirely.
- Really?
No.
I thought it'd be all posing.
I didn't think I'd find someone like you.
You're the only person
at that school who dares to be real.
Even my cousin, despite what happened,
just wants to be like everybody else.
We all want to fit in.
I don't. At least,
not where I'm supposed to.
Neither do I.
And still, today I felt that I fit in
for the first time in a long while.
What's wrong?
What's that tattoo?
I haven't seen it before.
- It's just a tattoo.
- I know what it means.
Let's go!
They shall not pass!
Go!
Shit. Not this way.
Come on!
- I didn't do anything!
- Really?
Let me go, please! Eric!
Eric!
Are you okay?
Yeah. Omar hasn't texted me.
Why didn't he come?
I don't want to ruin your night, Iván.
You're not ruining anything.
If you need to talk, I'm here for you.
Okay.
We'll vent to each other on one condition.
What's that?
We have to keep dancing.
Let's dance, then.
I understand Omar's traumatized
and he isn't over it,
but he should understand going
to Las Encinas is important for me.
What's wrong with changing? Huh?
Why should I settle for a shitty life?
Deleting his message was hard.
But you can't live in the past.
Exactly.
That's life.
It changes overnight.
Look at me.
All you can do is keep looking ahead.
And live in the moment.
Like this one.
I'm going outside to call Nico.
The signal here is bad.
If you see him, tell him to wait for me.
Honey, can't you see
he isn't replying for a reason?
It doesn't matter what he says
or how many chances you give him.
If you're not someone's priority,
you'll never be.
He'll just keep treating you like shit.
You'll be thinking,
"One day he'll notice me."
But he won't.
It's like being invisible.
You should get over him
by fucking someone else.
That's it, isn't it?
You fuck your problems away.
It's not about fucking, Chloe.
It's about creating real bonds.
Intimacy, affection… Sound familiar?
I guess not.
You lash out whenever I show I care.
- Maybe I don't want those things.
- Maybe you're scared.
You hide your true self so people
won't find out you have real depth.
And then you need to act on your feelings.
I'm not saying this to hurt you.
I'm trying to give you a wake-up call.
Hey. Are you coming to the party?
Isn't that against the rules?
Joel's upstairs, right?
Yeah. Why? What's wrong?
They were just dancing.
This is misleading.
Really?
I'm losing my fucking mind.
Why the hell am I doing this?
If I trust him, I trust him.
Let's go for a walk.
You can get some fresh air.
Hey. Have you seen Sonia?
She just left, hon.
She got tired of waiting for you.
Come on.
This bottle has both our names on it.
Can I borrow your phone?
Mine died, and I need to call Sonia.
You've already hurt her enough.
Give me that.
You need to leave her alone.
Drink and let live. Trust me.
- Wait, my cousin and Sonia…
- What about them?
- Nothing. But you're into him, right?
- I mean…
Let's see if I understand.
You're selling me on your cousin
while I'm undressing you?
No. I'm just saying it's only natural
that you like him. He's great, and he's-
- Yeah, he's great.
- He has it all.
Let's see.
Your cousin is a great fuck,
but I'm sure you're better.
One sec. When I have sex-
What do you need to explain?
Shut up and fuck me.
It's too much for me.
It's not only Joel but the app too.
I'm not sure
I'm the right person to run it.
- You are. You care about people.
- What if I'm not good enough?
What if someone gets hurt?
You can't control everything, Omar.
People are responsible for themselves.
Don't tell anyone about this.
If your offer to help still stands,
I'd like to find out who's sending these.
I JUST WANT TO STOP BEING INVISIBLE.
Any idea who it might be?
He'll just keep treating you like shit.
You'll be thinking,
"One day he'll notice me."
But he won't. It's like being invisible.
I think I do.
Bye, handsome.
I need to go to work.
Hey. Have you seen my cousin?
No, I haven't.
Nico!
Rocío's been arrested.
What?
I couldn't do anything.
You left her alone?
What was I supposed to do?
Get arrested too?
I just wanted you
not to get yourself into trouble.
Or me or my friends.
Was that too much to ask?
What about you?
What were you doing
while she was arrested?
I thought you left.
I wanted to apologize for what I said.
Chloe!
I didn't do it to hurt you.
It was a wake-up call.
He doesn't care about you.
I thought you needed help,
but I see you're just a grade-A bitch.
PLAYLIST FOR CHLOE BY ERIC
Fuck!
I don't like it when we argue.
I love you.
Whatever happens.
I love you too.
I'm scared of losing you.
YOU'VE BEEN ADDED TO
THE LAS ENCINAS SELF-DEFENSE GROUP
JESSICA
CLASSES START TOMORROW
Thanks for spending
this special evening with us.
But this wouldn't be a birthday
without a present, right?
You've seen plenty of bling tonight,
but this moment
is going to shine the brightest.
After all we've been through,
nothing can keep us apart.
One, two!
SPORTS AREA
Sara,
will you marry me?
So here are your options.
Stay with him
and pray to God that it all goes well,
or learn self-defense
in case it goes wrong.
Subtitle translation by: Toni Navarro,
Meredith Cannella